Hey, did you know
that three dates with the same woman...
(Howard:)...is the threshold for sex?
(Raj:)Actually, I've never had three dates
with the same woman.
(Leonard:)With Penny and me, it took two years.
But now that I think about it,
that was three dates.
(Howard:)Okay, well,
before you and Penny hooked up...
(Howard:)...did she ask
for any kind of commitment?
(Leonard:)No, she was pretty clear
about wanting to keep her options open.
(Sheldon(arriving):)I have something to announce,
but out of respect for convention...
(Sheldon(arriving):)...I will wait for you
to finish your conversation.
(Sheldon(arriving):)What are you talking about?
(Leonard:)The cultural paradigm in which
people have sex after three dates.
(Sheldon:)I see.
Now, are we talking "date"
the social interaction...
...or "date" the dried fruit?
(Howard:)Never mind.
What's your announcement?
SHELDON:
Oh, good, my turn.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is very exciting, and I wanted
you to be among the first to know--
I hear you're gonna be on the radio...
...with Ira Flatow from Science Friday
next week.